{
  "General": [
    {
      "Question": "Who created this bot?",
      "Answer": "Blurr",
      "Options": [
        "Knight",
        "Kruze",
        "Frazzle"
      ],
      "Seconds": 13
    },
    {
      "Question": "What is the legal age to buy alcohol in England?",
      "Answer": "18",
      "Options": [
        "16",
        "21",
        "20"
      ],
      "Seconds": 13
    },
    {
      "Question": "How many eyes does a bee have?",
      "Answer": "5",
      "Options": [
        "2",
        "4",
        "1"
      ],
      "Seconds": 13
    },
    {
      "Question": "Which animal can be seen on the Porsche logo?",
      "Answer": "Horse",
      "Options": [
        "Snake",
        "Lizard",
        "Cheetah"
      ],
      "Seconds": 13
    },
    {
      "Question": "Which country produces the most coffee in the world?",
      "Answer": "Brazil",
      "Options": [
        "USA",
        "India",
        "Ghana"
      ],
      "Seconds": 13
    },
    {
      "Question": "Which country invented tea?",
      "Answer": "China",
      "Options": [
        "England",
        "India",
        "Spain"
      ],
      "Seconds": 13
    },
    {
      "Question": "Which kind of alcohol is Russia notoriously known for?",
      "Answer": "Vodka",
      "Options": [
        "Rum",
        "Dark Fruit Cider",
        "Champagne"
      ],
      "Seconds": 13
    },
    {
      "Question": "What is the national dish of Spain?",
      "Answer": "Paella",
      "Options": [
        "Gazpacho",
        "Tortilla Española",
        "Gambas al ajillo"
      ],
      "Seconds": 13
    },
    {
      "Question": "Which European nation was said to invent hot dogs?",
      "Answer": "Germany",
      "Options": [
        "England",
        "Spain",
        "Belgium"
      ],
      "Seconds": 13
    },
    {
      "Question": "Which country is responsible for giving us pizza and pasta?",
      "Answer": "Italy",
      "Options": [
        "Germany",
        "India",
        "England"
      ],
      "Seconds": 13
    },
    {
      "Question": "What is the name of the world’s longest river?",
      "Answer": "The Nile",
      "Options": [
        "River Thames",
        "Amazon",
        "Yangtze"
      ],
      "Seconds": 13
    },
    {
      "Question": "What is the capital of Australia?",
      "Answer": "Canberra",
      "Options": [
        "Sydney",
        "Melbourne",
        "Queensland"
      ],
      "Seconds": 13
    },
    {
      "Question": "Which of these countries does NOT have a London?",
      "Answer": "Australia",
      "Options": [
        "England",
        "Canada",
        "USA"
      ],
      "Seconds": 13
    },
    {
      "Question": "Whats the fastest land animal in the world?",
      "Answer": "Cheetah",
      "Options": [
        "Quarter Horse",
        "Lion",
        "Blackbuck"
      ],
      "Seconds": 13
    },
    {
      "Question": "Who was one of the writers of Seinfeld?",
      "Answer": "Larry David",
      "Options": [
        "Martin scorese",
        "Harvey Weinstein",
        "Adam McKay"
      ],
      "Seconds": 13
    },
    {
      "Question": "How many Harry Potter books and movies are there?",
      "Answer": "7 books and 8 movies",
      "Options": [
        "8 books and 7 movies",
        "7 books and 7 movies",
        "6 movies and 7 books"
      ],
      "Seconds": 13
    },
  ],
  "Sports": [
    {
      "Question": "Who won the 2014 Fifa World Cup in Brazil?",
      "Answer": "Germany",
      "Options": [
        "Brazil",
        "England",
        "Netherlands"
      ],
      "Seconds": 13
    },
    {
      "Question": "How many players are on a Football/Soccer side?",
      "Answer": "11",
      "Options": [
        "8",
        "10",
        "12"
      ],
      "Seconds": 12
    },
    {
      "Question": "How many players are on a Rugby side?",
      "Answer": "15",
      "Options": [
        "11",
        "8",
        "16"
      ],
      "Seconds": 12
    },
    {
      "Question": "What is Usain Bolt’s 100m world record time?",
      "Answer": "9.58",
      "Options": [
        "9.47",
        "10.01",
        "9.55"
      ],
      "Seconds": 12
    },
    {
      "Question": "Which England footballer was famously never given a yellow card?",
      "Answer": "Lineker",
      "Options": [
        "Rooney",
        "Lampard",
        "Giggs"
      ],
      "Seconds": 12
    },
    {
      "Question": "How many times has Roger Federer won the French Open?",
      "Answer": "1",
      "Options": [
        "2",
        "3",
        "4"
      ],
      "Seconds": 12
    },
    {
      "Question": "The LA Lakers and New York Knicks play which sport?",
      "Answer": "NBA",
      "Options": [
        "NFL",
        "AFL",
        "MLB"
      ],
      "Seconds": 12
    },
    {
      "Question": "Katarina Johnson-Thompson is world champion in which sport?",
      "Answer": "Heptathlon",
      "Options": [
        "Triaphlon",
        "Taekwondo",
        "Modern Pentathlon"
      ],
      "Seconds": 12
    },
    {
      "Question": "Which country did F1 legend Ayrton Senna come from?",
      "Answer": "Brazil",
      "Options": [
        "Argentina",
        "Spain",
        "USA"
      ],
      "Seconds": 12
    },
    {
      "Question": "A penalty in football/soccer is taken how many yards away from the goal?",
      "Answer": "12",
      "Options": [
        "10",
        "8",
        "15"
      ],
      "Seconds": 12
    },
    {
      "Question": "Who did Cristiano Ronaldo make his Premier League debut against in 2003?",
      "Answer": "Bolton Wanderers",
      "Options": [
        "Manchester United",
        "Liverpool FC",
        "Wolverhampton Wanderers FC"
      ],
      "Seconds": 13
    },
    {
      "Question": "In what year did Andy Murray win Wimbledon for the first time?",
      "Answer": "2013",
      "Options": [
        "2012",
        "2015",
        "2010"
      ],
      "Seconds": 13
    },
    {
      "Question": "Which country will host the 2024 Olympic and Paralympic Games?",
      "Answer": "France",
      "Options": [
        "Brazil",
        "Russia",
        "Qatar"
      ],
      "Seconds": 13
    },
    {
      "Question": "Who did England beat in the 2019 cricket World Cup final?",
      "Answer": "New Zealand",
      "Options": [
        "Australia",
        "Ireland",
        "Wales"
      ],
      "Seconds": 13
    }
  ],
  "Motorsports": [
    {
      "Question": "Who was the MotoGP Champion in 2009?",
      "Answer": "Valentino Rossi",
      "Options": [
        "Jorge Lorenzo",
        "Casey Stoner",
        "Marc Márquez"
      ],
      "Seconds": 13
    },
    {
      "Question": "Where was the FIM Motocross of Nations hosted in 2019?",
      "Answer": "The Netherlands",
      "Options": [
        "England",
        "France",
        "Switzerland"
      ],
      "Seconds": 13
    },
    {
      "Question": "How many times has Jorge Lorenzo been MotoGP Champion?",
      "Answer": "3",
      "Options": [
        "2",
        "5",
        "6"
      ],
      "Seconds": 13
    },
    {
      "Question": "What is the fastest average speed at the Isle of Man TT?",
      "Answer": "135.452mph",
      "Options": [
        "134.632mph",
        "152.456mph",
        "153.645mph"
      ],
      "Seconds": 13
    },
    {
      "Question": "Who was the first winner of the Isle of Man TT?",
      "Answer": "Charles Collier",
      "Options": [
        "Joey Dunlop",
        "Peter Hickman",
        "Ben Birchall"
      ],
      "Seconds": 13
    },
    {
      "Question": "How many times has Joey Dunlop won the Isle of Man TT?",
      "Answer": "26",
      "Options": [
        "23",
        "19",
        "17"
      ],
      "Seconds": 13
    },
    {
      "Question": "How many times has Michael Dunlop won the Isle of Man TT?",
      "Answer": "19",
      "Options": [
        "23",
        "26",
        "17"
      ],
      "Seconds": 13
    },
    {
      "Question": "How many F1 championships has Lewis Hamilton won?",
      "Answer": "6",
      "Options": [
        "8",
        "5",
        "4"
      ],
      "Seconds": 13
    },
    {
      "Question": "Which circuit has the highest capacity for spectators?",
      "Answer": "Circuit de la Sarthe",
      "Options": [
        "Shanghai International Circuit",
        "Indianapolis Motor Speedway",
        "Brands Hatch"
      ],
      "Seconds": 13
    },
    {
      "Question": "Juan Pablo Montoya still holds the record for the fastest average lap speed in an F1 car. At which track did he reach 231.5mph in 2005?",
      "Answer": "Monza",
      "Options": [
        "Suzuka",
        "Mugello",
        "Interlagos"
      ],
      "Seconds": 13
    },
    {
      "Question": "Arrabiata 1 & 2 can be found at which circuit?",
      "Answer": "Mugello",
      "Options": [
        "Misano",
        "Magione",
        "Monza"
      ],
      "Seconds": 13
    },
    {
      "Question": "Which British track is the oldest race track in the world?",
      "Answer": "Brooklands",
      "Options": [
        "Cadwell Park",
        "Donington Park",
        "Brands Hatch"
      ],
      "Seconds": 13
    },
    {
      "Question": "At which corner at which track did Ayrton Senna say he could speak to God?",
      "Answer": "Eau Rouge - Spa",
      "Options": [
        "Parabolica - Monza",
        "Bico do Pato - Interlagos",
        "Senna 'S' - Autódromo"
      ],
      "Seconds": 13
    },
    {
      "Question": "Pikes Peak International Hill Climb, aka The Race to the Clouds has how many turns over the 20km course?",
      "Answer": "156",
      "Options": [
        "172",
        "98",
        "72"
      ],
      "Seconds": 13
    },
    {
      "Question": "274 people have died at the world's most dangerous 'race track' on the Isle of Man but who holds the Senior TT lap record?",
      "Answer": "Peter Hickman",
      "Options": [
        "Joey Dunlop",
        "John McGuinness",
        "Guy Martin"
      ],
      "Seconds": 13
    },
    {
      "Question": "Which production car holds the fastest lap at the notorious Nürburgring?",
      "Answer": "Lamborghini Aventador LP770-4 SVJ",
      "Options": [
        "Porsche 918 Spyder",
        "Nissan GT-R Nismo",
        "McLaren P1"
      ],
      "Seconds": 13
    },
    {
      "Question": "Which track is home to the famous 'Corkscrew' corner?",
      "Answer": "Laguna Seca",
      "Options": [
        "Sachsenring",
        "Suzuka",
        "Spa"
      ],
      "Seconds": 13
    },
    {
      "Question": "Who holds the MotoGP lap record at Mugello?",
      "Answer": "Marc Marquez",
      "Options": [
        "Valentino Rossi",
        "Nicky Hayden",
        "Casey Stoner"
      ],
      "Seconds": 13
    },
    {
      "Question": "Who won the 2006 MotoGP Championship?",
      "Answer": "Nicky Hayden",
      "Options": [
        "Dani Pedrosa",
        "Valentino Rossi",
        "Casey Stoner"
      ],
      "Seconds": 12
    },
    {
      "Question": "How many podium finishes has Nicky Hayden had in the MotoGP class?",
      "Answer": "28",
      "Options": [
        "30",
        "26",
        "24"
      ],
      "Seconds": 13
    },
    {
      "Question": "When did MotoGP last race at Laguna Seca?",
      "Answer": "2013",
      "Options": [
        "2012",
        "2010",
        "2009"
      ],
      "Seconds": 13
    },
    {
      "Question": "When did Valentino Rossi last win a MotoGP Championship?",
      "Answer": "2009",
      "Options": [
        "2008",
        "2012",
        "2014"
      ],
      "Seconds": 13
    },
    {
      "Question": "When was the last time a rider won the MotoGP Championship that was not Spanish?",
      "Answer": "Casey Stoner (AUS) - 2011",
      "Options": [
        "Valentino Rossi (ITA) - 2009",
        "Nicky Hayden (USA) - 2006",
        "Cal Crutchlow (GBR) - 2015"
      ],
      "Seconds": 13
    },
    {
      "Question": "Which of the following is NOT an Italian MotoGP rider?",
      "Answer": "Fabio Quartararo",
      "Options": [
        "Valentino Rossi",
        "Marco Simoncelli",
        "Andrea Dovizioso"
      ],
      "Seconds": 13
    }
  ],
  "Gaming": [
    {
      "Question": "Vanilla Minecraft - How many doors are crafted with 6 wooden planks?",
      "Answer": "3",
      "Options": [
        "1",
        "6",
        "5"
      ],
      "Seconds": 13
    },
    {
      "Question": "Rainbow Six: Siege - Which of the following is NOT a unit?",
      "Answer": "MI5",
      "Options": [
        "SAS",
        "REU",
        "Jaeger Corps"
      ],
      "Seconds": 13
    },
    {
      "Question": "Rainbow 6: Siege - What is the operator Mira's full name?",
      "Answer": "Dr. Elena María Álvarez",
      "Options": [
        "Liu Tze Long",
        "Meghan Castellano",
        "Tina Lin Tsang"
      ],
      "Seconds": 13
    },
    {
      "Question": "When is Steam's birthday?",
      "Answer": "12 September 2003",
      "Options": [
        "16 September 2004",
        "10 September 2002",
        "25 September 2004"
      ],
      "Seconds": 10
    },
    {
      "Question": "What year was Ubisoft founded?",
      "Answer": "1986",
      "Options": [
        "1994",
        "2001",
        "1998"
      ],
      "Seconds": 10
    },
    {
      "Question": "What year was Rockstar Games founded?",
      "Answer": "1998",
      "Options": [
        "1995",
        "2002",
        "1988"
      ],
      "Seconds": 10
    },
    {
      "Question": "What year was Electronic Arts founded?",
      "Answer": "1982",
      "Options": [
        "1992",
        "2005",
        "1989"
      ],
      "Seconds": 10
    },
    {
      "Question": "Where are the Rockstar North headquaters?",
      "Answer": "Scotland",
      "Options": [
        "North London",
        "San Francisco",
        "Canada"
      ],
      "Seconds": 10
    },
    {
      "Question": "Where are the Activision headquaters?",
      "Answer": "California",
      "Options": [
        "Scotland",
        "Monaco",
        "Montreal"
      ],
      "Seconds": 10
    },
    {
      "Question": "Where are the Ubisoft headquaters?",
      "Answer": "Montreuil",
      "Options": [
        "Montreal",
        "Monaco",
        "Milan"
      ],
      "Seconds": 10
    },
    {
      "Question": "Who are the developers of Tom Clancy's Rainbow Six: Siege?",
      "Answer": "Ubisoft Montreal",
      "Options": [
        "Ubisoft Paris",
        "Electronic Arts",
        "Activision"
      ],
      "Seconds": 10
    },
    {
      "Question": "How many playable characters are there in the Grand Theft Auto V single player mode?",
      "Answer": "3",
      "Options": [
        "1",
        "2",
        "4"
      ],
      "Seconds": 10
    },
    {
      "Question": "Which of the following games series is NOT Tom Clancy's?",
      "Answer": "Sniper: Ghost Warrior",
      "Options": [
        "Rainbow Six",
        "Ghost Recon",
        "The Division"
      ],
      "Seconds": 10
    }
  ],
  "Movies": [
    {
      "Question": "Who was the director of Star Wars: The Force Awakens?",
      "Answer": "J.J. Abrams",
      "Options": [
        "Carrie Fisher",
        "Rian Johnson",
        "George Lucas"
      ],
      "Seconds": 12
    },
    {
      "Question": "How much did Disney buy the Star Wars franchise for?",
      "Answer": "$4.05 billion",
      "Options": [
        "$4.8 billion",
        "$2.3 billion",
        "$3.1 billion"
      ],
      "Seconds": 12
    },
    {
      "Question": "How much did Avengers: Endgame gross at the box office?",
      "Answer": "$2.8 billion",
      "Options": [
        "$3.1 billion",
        "$2.1 billion",
        "$3 billion"
      ],
      "Seconds": 10
    },
    {
      "Question": "Which character is played by Chris Hemsworth in the Avengers series?",
      "Answer": "Thor",
      "Options": [
        "Captain America",
        "Star-Lord",
        "Groot"
      ],
      "Seconds": 10
    },
    {
      "Question": "What is the earliest surviving motion-picture film, showing actual consecutive action?",
      "Answer": "Roundhay Garden Scene",
      "Options": [
        "Arrival of a Train",
        "Departure of Miss Staples",
        "Horse Racing Show"
      ],
      "Seconds": 13
    }
  ],
  "Music": [
    {
      "Question": "What was the name of the group Justin Timberlake used to be part of?",
      "Answer": "N' Sync",
      "Options": [
        "The Ordinary Boys",
        "Scouting For Girls",
        "The Thrills"
      ],
      "Seconds": 13
    },
    {
      "Question": "Which country did AC/DC originate in?",
      "Answer": "Australia",
      "Options": [
        "England",
        "Scotland",
        "Ireland"
      ],
      "Seconds": 13
    },
    {
      "Question": "What genre of music did Taylor Swift start in?",
      "Answer": "Country",
      "Options": [
        "Pop",
        "Rap",
        "Reggae"
      ],
      "Seconds": 13
    },
    {
      "Question": "Which musical legend is Jay-Z married to?",
      "Answer": "Beyonce",
      "Options": [
        "Elton John",
        "Rihanna",
        "Selena Gomez"
      ],
      "Seconds": 13
    },
    {
      "Question": "How many Grammys does John Legend have?",
      "Answer": "10",
      "Options": [
        "11",
        "6",
        "8"
      ],
      "Seconds": 13
    },
    {
      "Question": "Which British group had a member by the name of Mel B?",
      "Answer": "Spice Girls",
      "Options": [
        "N-Dubz",
        "Pussycat Dolls",
        "Little Mix"
      ],
      "Seconds": 13
    }
  ],
  "Science": [
    {
      "Question": "Humans and chimpanzees share roughly how much DNA?",
      "Answer": "98%",
      "Options": [
        "100%",
        "66%",
        "74%"
      ],
      "Seconds": 13
    },
    {
      "Question": "How many light hours away is the sun from Neptune?",
      "Answer": "4.1",
      "Options": [
        "101.5",
        "16.2",
        "45.9"
      ],
      "Seconds": 13
    },
    {
      "Question": "What is the most abundant gas in the Earth’s atmosphere?",
      "Answer": "Nitrogen",
      "Options": [
        "Oxygen",
        "Argon",
        "Carbon Dioxide"
      ],
      "Seconds": 13
    },
    {
      "Question": "Roughly how long does it take for the sun’s light to reach Earth?",
      "Answer": "8 minutes",
      "Options": [
        "8 hours",
        "8 days",
        "8 seconds"
      ],
      "Seconds": 13
    },
    {
      "Question": "Which famous British physicist wrote A Brief History of Time?",
      "Answer": "Stephen Hawking",
      "Options": [
        "Isaac Newton",
        "Albert Einstein",
        "Charles Messier"
      ],
      "Seconds": 13
    },
    {
      "Question": "At what temperature are Celsius and Fahrenheit equal?",
      "Answer": "-40",
      "Options": [
        "40",
        "-15",
        "0"
      ],
      "Seconds": 13
    },
    {
      "Question": "What modern-day country was Marie Curie born in?",
      "Answer": "Poland",
      "Options": [
        "Germany",
        "The Netherlands",
        "Czech Republic"
      ],
      "Seconds": 13
    },
    {
      "Question": "What is the biggest planet in our solar system?",
      "Answer": "Jupiter",
      "Options": [
        "Saturn",
        "The Sun",
        "Uranus"
      ],
      "Seconds": 13
    },
    {
      "Question": "What name is given for the number of protons found in the nucleus of an atom?",
      "Answer": "Atomic number",
      "Options": [
        "Pronucleas Number",
        "Equal Number",
        "Identical Number"
      ],
      "Seconds": 13
    },
    {
      "Question": "How many vertebrae does the average human possess?",
      "Answer": "33",
      "Options": [
        "32",
        "30",
        "29"
      ],
      "Seconds": 13
    },
    {
      "Question": "What was the name of the first man-made satellite launched by the Soviet Union in 1957?",
      "Answer": "Sputnik 1",
      "Options": [
        "Sputnik 100",
        "1-Sputnik",
        "100-Sputnik"
      ],
      "Seconds": 13
    },
    {
      "Question": "Which oath of ethics taken by doctors is named after an Ancient Greek physician?",
      "Answer": "Hippocratic Oath",
      "Options": [
        "Herophilos Oath",
        "Erasistratus Oath",
        "Empedocles Oath"
      ],
      "Seconds": 13
    },
    {
      "Question": "What is a material that will not carry an electrical charge called?",
      "Answer": "Insulator",
      "Options": [
        "Slator",
        "Inslator",
        "Sulator"
      ],
      "Seconds": 13
    },
    {
      "Question": "Which Apollo moon mission was the first to carry a lunar rover?",
      "Answer": "Apollo 15",
      "Options": [
        "Apollo 20",
        "Apollo 13",
        "Apollo 17"
      ],
      "Seconds": 13
    },
    {
      "Question": "How many teeth does an adult human have?",
      "Answer": "32",
      "Options": [
        "30",
        "34",
        "35"
      ],
      "Seconds": 13
    },
    {
      "Question": "What is the study of mushrooms called?",
      "Answer": "Mycology",
      "Options": [
        "Mythology",
        "Shroomology",
        "Fyngology"
      ],
      "Seconds": 13
    },
    {
      "Question": "On the periodic table, what symbol stands for silver?",
      "Answer": "Ag",
      "Options": [
        "Si",
        "Sv",
        "Av"
      ],
      "Seconds": 13
    },
    {
      "Question": "Which two planets lack moons?",
      "Answer": "Mercury and Venus",
      "Options": [
        "Mars and Venus",
        "Jupiter and Saturn",
        "Mars and Saturn"
      ],
      "Seconds": 13
    },
    {
      "Question": "How many hearts do octopuses have?",
      "Answer": "Three",
      "Options": [
        "Two",
        "Five",
        "Eight"
      ],
      "Seconds": 13
    },
    {
      "Question": "In electronics, what does DC stand for?",
      "Answer": "Direct Current",
      "Options": [
        "Dimmer Current",
        "Delta Current",
        "Demagnetized Current"
      ],
      "Seconds": 13
    },
    {
      "Question": "What was the name of the first supersonic passenger airliner?",
      "Answer": "Concorde",
      "Options": [
        "Lightning",
        "Skyray",
        "Super Sabre"
      ],
      "Seconds": 13
    }
  ],
  "Art": [
    {
      "Question": "Who created the Mona Lisa?",
      "Answer": "Leonardo da Vinci",
      "Options": [
        "Pablo Picasso",
        "Andy Warhol",
        "Vincent Van Gogh "
      ],
      "Seconds": 10
    },
    {
      "Question": "Which two cities provide the setting for Charles Dickens’ ‘A Tale of Two Cities’?",
      "Answer": "London and Paris",
      "Options": [
        "Brussels and Amsterdam",
        "Paris and Monaco",
        "Amsterdam and Milan"
      ],
      "Seconds": 10
    },
    {
      "Question": "The Mona Lisa is on display in which Paris museum?",
      "Answer": "Louvre",
      "Options": [
        "Rodin",
        "Rmn-Grand",
        "Carnavalet"
      ],
      "Seconds": 10
    },
    {
      "Question": "Which artist painted the Poppy Field in 1873?",
      "Answer": "Claude Monet",
      "Options": [
        "Vincent van Gogh",
        "Pablo Picasso",
        "Aleister Crowley"
      ],
      "Seconds": 10
    },
    {
      "Question": "What is the name of the fourth book in the Harry Potter series?",
      "Answer": "Harry Potter and the Goblet of Fire",
      "Options": [
        "Harry Potter and the Cursed Child",
        "Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows",
        "Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban"
      ],
      "Seconds": 10
    },
    {
      "Question": "The Creation of Adam is one of nine scenes featured on the ceiling of which Rome landmark?",
      "Answer": "The Sistine Chapel",
      "Options": [
        "Colosseum",
        "Roman Forum",
        "Trevi Fountain"
      ],
      "Seconds": 10
    },
    {
      "Question": "Which Shakespeare play is the following quote from? 'The course of true love never did run smooth'",
      "Answer": "A Midsummer Night's Dream",
      "Options": [
        "Hamlet",
        "Romeo and Juliet",
        "Julius Caesar"
      ],
      "Seconds": 13
    },
    {
      "Question": "Who wrote the Curious Incident of the Dog in the Night Time?",
      "Answer": "Mark Haddon",
      "Options": [
        "Amin Maalouf",
        "Hector-Henri Malot",
        "Julian Clare May"
      ],
      "Seconds": 10
    },
    {
      "Question": "In which century did Leonardo da Vinci paint The Last Supper?",
      "Answer": "15th Century",
      "Options": [
        "17th Century",
        "20th Century",
        "18th Century"
      ],
      "Seconds": 10
    },
    {
      "Question": "The Tate is a network of four art museums; two are based in London, give the other two English locations?",
      "Answer": "Liverpool and Cornwall",
      "Options": [
        "Manchester and Blackpool",
        "Cornwall and Kent",
        "Sheffield and Bath"
      ],
      "Seconds": 13
    },
    {
      "Question": "What are the names of the three ‘Darling’ children in J.M. Barrie’s ‘Peter Pan’?",
      "Answer": "Wendy, John and Michael",
      "Options": [
        "John, Michael and William",
        "William, John and Wendy",
        "Wendy, William and Michael"
      ],
      "Seconds": 10
    },
    {
      "Question": "Who created the famous sculpture 'The Thinker'?",
      "Answer": "Auguste Rodin",
      "Options": [
        "Alexandros of Antioch",
        "Michelangelo",
        "Ian Walters"
      ],
      "Seconds": 10
    },
    {
      "Question": "Which Emily Brontë novel is the inspiration for a Kate Bush song?",
      "Answer": "Wuthering Heights",
      "Options": [
        "No Coward",
        "The Night is Darkening Round Me",
        "Gondal's Queen"
      ],
      "Seconds": 10
    },
    {
      "Question": "Sir Quentin Saxby Blake is an English cartoonist, illustrator and children's writer best known for illustrating books by which author?",
      "Answer": "Roald Dahl",
      "Options": [
        "George Orwell",
        "Zadie Smith",
        "Charlotte Bronte"
      ],
      "Seconds": 13
    },
    {
      "Question": "Which Shakespearean play features the characters of Goneril, Regan and Cordelia?",
      "Answer": "King Lear",
      "Options": [
        "Romeo and Juliet",
        "The Tempest",
        "Twelfth Night"
      ],
      "Seconds": 12
    },
    {
      "Question": "In which city would you find The Van Gogh Museum?",
      "Answer": "Amsterdam",
      "Options": [
        "London",
        "Manchester",
        "Brussels"
      ],
      "Seconds": 10
    },
    {
      "Question": "Which two primary colours could you mix together to make purple when painting?",
      "Answer": "Red and Blue",
      "Options": [
        "Blue and Green",
        "Green and Red",
        "Blue and Yellow"
      ],
      "Seconds": 12
    },
    {
      "Question": "The Hunger Games young adult series was written by which author?",
      "Answer": "Suzanne Collins",
      "Options": [
        "Gary Ross",
        "Billy Ray",
        "Peter Craig"
      ],
      "Seconds": 12
    },
    {
      "Question": "Who created the Angel of the North?",
      "Answer": "Antony Gormley",
      "Options": [
        "Eric Gill",
        "Henry Moore",
        "Thomas Heatherwick"
      ],
      "Seconds": 10
    },
    {
      "Question": "Which famous work of literature opens with these lines? 'Two households, both alike in dignity, in fair Verona, where we lay our scene…'",
      "Answer": "Romeo and Juliet",
      "Options": [
        "Commonwealth",
        "Arcadia",
        "The History of Love"
      ],
      "Seconds": 13
    },
    {
      "Question": "‘Guernica’, ‘The Weeping Woman’ and ‘Le Rêve’ are all works by the same artist. Can you name them?",
      "Answer": "Pablo Picasso",
      "Options": [
        "Vincent van Gogh",
        "Leonardo da Vinci",
        "Gustav Klimt"
      ],
      "Seconds": 10
    },
    {
      "Question": "What is the name of the pig in E.B. White’s Charlotte’s Web?",
      "Answer": "Wilbur",
      "Options": [
        "Wilbert",
        "Wilpar",
        "Wilnort"
      ],
      "Seconds": 10
    },
    {
      "Question": "Which book has the following opening line been taken from? 'These two very old people are the father and mother of Mr. Bucket.'",
      "Answer": "Charlie and the Chocolate Factory",
      "Options": [
        "Matilda",
        "The Witches",
        "James and the Giant Peach"
      ],
      "Seconds": 13
    },
    {
      "Question": "Which artist cut off the lobe of his own ear and later shot himself?",
      "Answer": "Vincent van Gogh",
      "Options": [
        "Leonardo da Vinci",
        "Harry Matisse",
        "Gustav Klimt"
      ],
      "Seconds": 10
    },
    {
      "Question": "How many lines are there in a sonnet?",
      "Answer": "14",
      "Options": [
        "10",
        "12",
        "15"
      ],
      "Seconds": 10
    },
    {
      "Question": "What artist sold a balloon dog for $58.4 million?",
      "Answer": "Jeff Koons",
      "Options": [
        "Mark Rothko",
        "Jasper Johns",
        "50 Cent"
      ],
      "Seconds": 10
    }
  ],
  "Anime": [

  ],
  "History": [

  ],
  "Computing": [
    {
      "Question": "How many bits in a byte?",
      "Answer": "8",
      "Options": [
        "6",
        "7",
        "10"
      ],
      "Seconds": 13
    },
    {
      "Question": "Which of the following is not part of a Hard Drive Disks physical structure?",
      "Answer": "Partition",
      "Options": [
        "Main Spindle",
        "Head Stack Assembly",
        "Platter"
      ],
      "Seconds": 13
    },
    {
      "Question": "Which of the following is not a type of storage device?",
      "Answer": "Disk Image",
      "Options": [
        "RAM (Random Access Memory)",
        "USB Flash Memory",
        "Solid State Drive"
      ],
      "Seconds": 13
    },
    {
      "Question": "Which of the following is a hashing algorithm",
      "Answer": "MD5",
      "Options": [
        "HA5",
        "MH5",
        "CB-SEC"
      ],
      "Seconds": 13
    },
    {
      "Question": "What is the name of an attack that the attack tries multiple passwords with the hope of eventually guessing correctly?",
      "Answer": "Brute-Force Attack",
      "Options": [
        "Dictionary Attack",
        "Malware Attack",
        "Consistent Attack"
      ],
      "Seconds": 17
    },
    {
      "Question": "What are the words of the acronym CD-ROM?",
      "Answer": "Compact Disc Read Only Memory",
      "Options": [
        "Circular Disc Read Only Memory",
        "Circular Disc Read Only Meme",
        "Compact Disc Read Only Meme"
      ],
      "Seconds": 13
    },
    {
      "Question": "When working in Microsoft Internet Explorer, in 2013, what is the shortcut to open the window to your favorites?",
      "Answer": "Ctrl-B",
      "Options": [
        "Ctrl-S",
        "Ctrl-F",
        "Ctrl-Alt-F"
      ],
      "Seconds": 13
    },
    {
      "Question": "What is the conversion of the base-2 number, 00000111, into base-10?",
      "Answer": "7",
      "Options": [
        "2",
        "6",
        "3"
      ],
      "Seconds": 13
    },
    {
      "Question": "When was the first personal computer made?",
      "Answer": "1974",
      "Options": [
        "1956",
        "1933",
        "1981"
      ],
      "Seconds": 13
    },
    {
      "Question": "When was the first silicon chip invented?",
      "Answer": "1961",
      "Options": [
        "1965",
        "1972",
        "1978"
      ],
      "Seconds": 13
    },
    {
      "Question": "When was the first cpu invented?",
      "Answer": "1971",
      "Options": [
        "1962",
        "1973",
        "1968"
      ],
      "Seconds": 13
    },
    {
      "Question": "Which is the correct definition for an API?",
      "Answer": "A set of functions and procedures allowing the creation of applications that access the features or data of an operating system, application, or other service.",
      "Options": [
        "Artificial intelligence used to access and analyse data from websites.",
        "A application used to get data from or send data to a server.",
        "Ariticial Practical Intelligence, used to practically simulate human like features such as walking, running and jumping in a humanoid robot."
      ],
      "Seconds": 15
    }
  ]
}